# **AZZAR BUDIYANTO**

Payaman - solokuro – lamongan, 62265 · +6282232529804 azzar.mr.zs@gmail.com · linkedin: azzar-budiyanto· azzarbudiyanto.me

Self-assured individual offering more than 3 years of **experience** as **Programmer**. Highly trained in various **technology** environments. Flexible and poised promoting well-developed skills in **IoT**, Web **development**, and **Microcontroller**.

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### 2018/10 - NOW

#### FREELANCER, NONE

- Enhanced production of a Product or Service to exceed goals.
- Developed effective **improvement** plans in alignment with goals and **specifications**.
- Developed and updated tracking spreadsheets for process monitoring and reporting.
- Generated reports detailing findings and **recommendations**.
- Planned **website development**, converting mockups into usable web presence with HTML, JavaScript, and Css coding.
- **Collaborated** with marketing, representing web team to **establish project goals**, projections and milestones.
- Designed, implemented and monitored web pages, plugins and functionality for continuous improvement.
- Develop an idea to actual object especially when using a microcontroller

#### 2020/09 - 2021/09

#### PHOTOGRAPHER, LEMBARAN KASIH

- Photographed high-quality images for various print and digital projects.
- Digitally edited photos to enhance appearance.
- Determined and adjusted subject position, props and lighting equipment while selecting camera angles to optimize final product.
- Edited, toned, captioned and uploaded photographs for publication.

#### 2020/01 - 2021/04

#### STUDENT AMBASSADOR, CICIL.CO.ID

- Smoothed registration processes, offered technical support and organized paperwork.
- Deal directly with **clients** regarding **administrative** issues.

#### 2022/01 - NOW

#### TRAINER, INDOBOT ACADEMY

- teaches material about arduino and its programming.
- monitor learning progress and prepare material for the next meeting.

#### **EDUCATION**

2012/07 - 2015/06

JUNIOR HIGH SCHOOL, SMP MUHAMMADIYAH 12 - SENDANGAGUNG

General education

2015/07 - 2018/06

SENIOR HIGH SCHOOL, MA AL-ISHLAH SENDANGAGUNG

Language, Science, And Religion

# **SKILLS**

## • **GENERAL**

- Office (word, exel, ppt)
- Web dev (ui, ux)

#### LANGUAGE

- english
- indonesian

# • TECHNICAL

- Microsoft office
- Canva
- Arduino

- Microcontroller programming
- lot experience
- Photography
- javanese
- arabic
- python
- C, C++, C#
- HTML, CSS, JS